[Music]
thank you
surely something else too
this afternoon she had noticed that one
of the floor tiles in the kitchen was
sticking up tile edges had always
protruded here and there
[Music]
it is the beautiful overcast autumn day
the perfect morning to stay in bed for
an extra 15 minutes and sip some
peppermint tea
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
slowly very often but today was
different and I enjoyed every moment of
it and even got to listen to an
audiobook I have to admit the weather
has reflected my mood and I'm feeling
peaceful a little tired and slower than
usual
pretty typical for the colder months I
think so I decided to work on a much
anticipated Autumn recipe I also plan to
spend the rest of the day working on
some new art projects as I've relocated
my artist studio and I'm attempting to
reopen my gift shop today hopefully all
goes as planned
[Music]
thank you
I thought I'd share something in this
video in hopes to spark a conversation
and that is one about seeking quality
friendships though I'm quite connected
in my community and enjoy quiet
socializing I only really have a couple
close friends this has always suited me
though everyone is different over the
years of navigating Human Relationships
I felt that some friendships have solid
foundations of love and respect others
grow out of less healthy root systems at
least in my experience
I asked what friendship challenges you
have faced throughout the years on
Instagram and many of you shared a
dislike of relationships that are built
upon constant gossip negativity bullying
or other practices that bring you down
and suck away your energy
it's a good reminder for all of us
especially this Autumn when we find
ourselves cozied up at home
to be wary of the words we use around
the people we care about I truly think
words have power to shape our
perceptions of ourselves in the world we
are what we think and speak after all
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
guys you need to try it it's so good if
you make poached pears this Autumn
please let me know what your experience
was think this is the most delicious
recipe I've tried in forever anyway I'm
sending you so much love and let's go
take a walk in the woods
thank you
[Music]
foreign
as I've grown and done my best to listen
to my soul and develop a more positive
mindset I admit I have lost friendships
often we've Grown Apart through having
less in common and wanting to be very
different types of people this is a
natural thing to happen as we change and
grow but it can be hard to accept as
I've gotten older I've been much less
interested in being critical of others
pessimistic and hard on myself and I no
longer gravitate towards friendships
defined by these things
I've started to treat my emotional
energy as a sacred Force I want to put
towards simply enjoying the time I have
left and spending it with people who are
just kind I guess
people who Inspire and make me feel safe
it's taken a long time to find those
friendships and it has forced me to
become comfortable with being on my own
sometimes I've had to be honest with
myself and humble as I have a tendency
to stand in my own way as we all do I
think happily I found my belonging it
just took time
foreign
[Music]
so as I wait with anticipation for the
leaves to begin falling from the Aspens
and Willows maybe it's time to consider
what you've been holding on to that
isn't serving you anymore and Let It Go
Autumn asks us to become thoughtful in
that way it is a mystical season where
things long hidden are brought to the
light especially within ourselves
[Music]
foreign I have spent the last couple
hours just hanging up my more autumnal
themed watercolors around the house and
I didn't remember how many kind of more
Autumn themed art pieces I had made
decorating for the season can be that
simple it could just be putting up some
leaves on the Windows updating my Autumn
wreath putting some pine cones here and
there for decoration it has been so
lovely this season to choose Simplicity
overall else and it has benefited me in
many ways it is interesting as well how
when you focus on Simplicity you notice
so many more opportunities for
decorating than you may have before for
example there was this free poster at my
bookstore inspired by a new book that
just came out called The Hidden World of
gnomes and so I thought I just had to
save it and bring it home and decorate
with it I thought it was just such a
sweet piece of art anyway I hope you all
have a absolutely wonderful day and you
stay warm if it's cold rain of your ads
that you can enjoy the seasons and allow
nature to teach you whatever it is that
you need to learn I think there's a lot
of things I needed to learn this season
and it has been a so far very thoughtful
very beneficial and fulfilling time so I
finished recording and then I realized
that I had forgotten something very
important and that was that I have
reopened my Etsy Shop I've had it closed
for about a month and I was working on a
lot of new art pieces and some new
projects and I'm happy to say Cottage
boxes are back in stock so many new
bookmark designs and I have kind of
revamped the entire store my Etsy Shop
is what has kept this channel going
throughout the years and I really
appreciate your support there is never
any obligation but I just want to let
you know that there were new art pieces
new fairy art autumnal art there's all
sorts of things maybe you'll take the
time to check it out but of course
there's never any application thank you
so much for your support of my work as
an artist and making music videos it
means the world and I'm so grateful I
can be here with you today so sending
you so much love and I will see you soon
goodbye
foreign
[Music]